extremescience.com 2010-01-12

# Extreme Science Privacy Policy

Extreme Science is committed to protecting your privacy on-line. We hope the following information will help you understand how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information You provide when visiting our website.

**Information \- How We Get It**   
Extreme Science collects data on website visitors who register for our opt-in newsletter service (the Extreme Science "E-Zine"). This information can only be collected by Extreme Science from users who voluntarily submit their information by entering it into a form and submitting it.

**Use of Cookies**   
Cookies are small text files placed on your computer's hard drive that enable websites to recognize repeat visitors. If you use the shopping cart in the Extreme Science Webstore, a cookie will be placed on your computer to "remember" the contents of your shopping cart.

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

**Third-Party Advertisements**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

**Log Files**   
Our server has a log file that tracks user sessions, i.e page views and downloaded files (for example, free wallpaper and calendar). We maintain these log files solely for our own internal purposes. Log files are not shared with third parties. 

**Sharing**  
Extreme Science does not share personal identification information with third parties. This information is maintained solely for our own internal purposes. 

**Links to Other Web Sites**   
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Extreme Science is not responsible for the privacy practices of other such sites. We encourage our subscribers to read the privacy statements of each and every website they visit. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by this website.

**Email Links**   
We use an email link to allow users to contact us directly with questions or comments. We read every message and we try to respond promptly where appropriate. We may file comments to improve the website. The comments are for internal use only and are not shared with third parties. 

**Email Communications to Requests for Information**   
In some cases, we send a confirmation email to verify that we have received the user's request for information. Email addresses provided to us to request information will be used to supply the requested information to the user. 

**Addresses**  
When website visitors request us to mail them information, or to ship product, we collect addresses. This information is not shared with any third parties. Any addresses we collect are used for mailing requested information to users, or to ship product that has been requested or won in a contest. 

**Required Disclosures**   
Extreme Science may disclose your personally identifiable information in the following circumstances: (1) Extreme Science is required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such disclosure is necessary to (i) conform to the edicts of the law; (ii) comply with legal process served upon Extreme Science; (iii) protect and defend the rights of the Extreme Science website, or other subscribers to the service or (iv) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of the Extreme Science website, subscribers or the general public; or (2) all or substantially all of the assets of Extreme Science are sold to a third party.
